Thank you.
Hmm? What are you thanking us for?
Kobito's birthday party yesterday.
I appreciate everything you guys did for her.
And I don't know, it made me feel good to know you care enough to go through all that trouble.
So thank you. You guys are awesome.
Whatever. There's no need to get all emotional about it.
That wasn't emotional. I just said thanks.
Regardless, the fact is, the party was great.
There are people all over this world who don't have friends to help them out when they need it.
So thank you, Kodaka, for reminding us every day should be a celebration of friends.
Yeah. We could have been cutting our own cake and singing to ourselves on our birthdays, you know?
But we don't frickin' have to.
It's not like I really need a reason to celebrate, though.
Kudos, big brother.
Rika? What's the matter with you?
Rika was just thinking about how excited she is to be working on the school festival.
She thinks we should stay focused.
Yeah, I guess you're right. That sounds like a good plan.
No, it doesn't. I'd rather hang out and talk about friendship.
But I get what Rika's trying to say without quite saying it.
And she's totally right.
We're here. What's up?
No, freaking what?
Cabbageo is the sweetest thing ever!
I could just beat you up on a better brine.
Ugh!
Is a cat cafe where you dress like cats?
Have you really never heard of one?
It's literally a cafe with cats running around
while you drink tea and drink tea.
I'm not sure what you're doing.
I'm not sure how to do it.
With cats running around while you drink tea and kick it.
No way!
For a town as depressing as this, that's actually pretty awesome.
Do whatever you want, I'm out.
I've got my hands full for the festival.
Oh, that's right. I forgot.
You said you were doing something with your class.
History of Toya, wasn't it?
Right!
I suggested we do the history of the almighty goddess Sena Kashiwazaki,
but all it did was remind the other girls in the class
how pitiful their lives were, so they said no.
Just thinking about it makes me want to hit someone in their kneecaps.
Well, if our resident idiot is out,
then there's no point in doing a comedy routine, is there?
That's too bad.
Next.
Whoa!
Just because Sena's not helping doesn't mean it's not a good option.
It was the worst option.
Rika agrees.
We're not that funny.
It would have been quite inappropriate.
My sources say the choice was crap.
Fine.
I get it.
It's done.
Kobito, you're here.
So does this mean you're skipping the middle school festival today to be with her?
Did your exhibit suck?
What were you going to do?
Yeah, tell us.
For inspiration.
Uh, most foolish kindred.
My mini secret shall never be known to you.
I guess that means I don't have to cook any more pork-flavored ramen.
Do you dare threaten the great racist V. Felicity Sumeragi, ruler of the majestic night in sky?
Ha-ha!
Foolish mortal.
I guess I get all the leftover meatloaf tonight, too.
Hey!
That's not fair!
Yes, it is.
Tell me and you can eat.
Fine.
It's a movie.
Like a real-life film?
That sounds like so much fun!
Hmm.
That might work.
So what are you doing?
Acting?
Directing?
What?
That is of no concern to you.
Cool.
I guess you don't mind being cut off from gaming.
I'm the lead.
Huh?
You're what?
I'm acting.
You're laughing?
For the third time, I'm acting!
I'm the cock-a-doodie lead, okay?
The movie is about me!
You're the lead?
That's amazing!
Congratulations!
I so want to see that movie!
Say he'll take me!
Okay, one thing at a time.
Kobito, if you're the lead, why are you here?
Don't they need you?
Oh, no.
You ditched them?
Listen to me.
Being picked as the lead's an honor.
You can't let them down.
They're...
Oh, no.
You ditched them?
Listen to me.
Being picked as the lead's an honor.
You can't let them down.
They're...
Oh, no.
You ditched them?
Listen to me.
It's an honor.
You can't let them down.
Hmm.
There are so many kids who never get chosen to do anything in class all year long, much
less be labeled the best.
Not even to be the line leader?
Nope.
Oh.
See?
You're lucky to have that chance, so be a rock star and make the best of it.
Isn't it cool to know that there are so many people in your class who need your awesomeness
to succeed?
Yeah, it is.
Just wait until they see what my racist v. Felicity Sumeragi ruler of the night can do.
Hmm.
Bye.
I shall be leaving you now.
Break your legs and arms out there, okay?
I bet we could make an even better movie for the festival.
Rika figured you were going to suggest that.
No objection here.
I think it's a great idea.
You already have your star, Ovs.
Yeah, I'm fine with a movie.
Sounds like a majority.
It's official.
Question.
Yeah?
What do you got, Rika?
Rika's a fan of filmmaking, but she wants to know what the plot will be.
Don't worry about that.
I've got it covered.
What do you mean you have it covered?
If you're thinking of writing the whole thing without us, it's going to be crap and
you know it.
Yeah, I can't understand a word if that's squawking, but I'm guessing you don't trust my creativity.
What creativity?
Come on, Yozara.
You know you don't have the greatest story writing resume.
Hmm.
I hear what you're saying, and I'm prepared to learn from my mistakes.
If you have any ideas about the plot, I'm willing to listen, so dry your eyes.
Let's do this.
Who has a suggestion?
I'll write it down and we can vote.
Maybe this time nobody has to get raped.
But what if it's tasteful?
Not the reaction I was expecting.
You crushed our dreams.
Ta-da!
I has arrived!
Poopy faces, consider your day made, and you are welcome.
That means everyone's here so we can get started.
So should we just tell you our ideas, or do you want us to write them down?
I'll write them up here on the board so we can see them and compare.
How about this?
A transfer student comes to a new country and everyone picks on him because of his accent,
but later they discover he's pretty cool and he becomes the most popular guy in class.
Um, the lead has to be a girl.
I require a juicy roll.
I require a giant juicy steak with french fries.
I don't care what the plot is, but I'd really like to play a samurai.
Rika thinks the boy student should meet another cute boy at school and have a steamy love scene.
Is there a way to make all that work together?
Hmm.
Let me just sleep on it tonight and then I can start spinning it all into gold.
It'll be the best script you ever read.
You get me.
Why are you messaging me this late?
All that to ask if I want to go to a movie with her.
But it makes sense to watch an actual movie before we make our own.
Maybe we'll get some ideas.
So tomorrow we'll just have the club meeting at the theater.
You get me.
Assuming C-U-Z means because.
Don't tell the others, huh?
Okay, understood.
Send.
Where are you?
Kodaka.
Are we going to a movie or do you have plans to assassinate someone in that ninja suit?
You think you're so funny. Let's go.
So which movie are we researching today?
I have no idea yet.
I figured I'd wait till we got here then pick from whatever's about to start.
Well, that's kind of random.
Hey, that's how I always pick movies. Don't judge me.
Hmm. How about this one?
Um.
That looks horrifying.
I'm guessing no.
No, it looks great. Why are we still standing here?
Well, I learned a lot.
Oh, shut up. No, you didn't. If I'd known it was going to be like that, I'd have never invited you.
Wasn't that bad.
So, if it wasn't so bad, then does that mean you might be open to doing something similar for our movie? Like just for pretend?
What did you say? I can't hear you.
Nothing. I just said I'm thirsty. Look there. That is a beautiful sunset that requires tea.
Okay, but this place serves tea, too.
Yeah, but I need a different kind of tea from a certain place, so follow me.
Meow. So cute.
Uh, did you just meow at them?
Meow.
Aw.
Nope. Nope. Oh, there you go. Good kitty. You caught it.
Meow.
You really have to like cats a lot to hang out in here.
There's no such thing as a person who doesn't like cats.
I'm gonna file that under debatable.
I'm gonna file you under shut up.
Don't you already have a cat at home you can plank with?
Nope. Our landlord won't allow it.
Besides, even if I could, I wouldn't want to get one.
Huh? Really? Why not?
Don't you remember when we were little, my cat Knight?
Ugh.
Come on, Knight, hurry up!
Yay! Good Knight!
Come here, Knight!
Knight!
Hey, Knight!
Come back, Knight!
I don't think I'll ever get over how hard it was to lose Knight like that.
Like, what's the point of getting close to someone or something if they're just going to leave?
It's much easier to keep my distance so it won't matter when they're gone.
Thanks for coming with me today.
Prepare your mind to be blown by an awesome script.
Can't wait.
This is kind of weird, but hanging out sort of made me feel like that again.
Like what?
You know, friends like we were 10 years ago.
I know what you mean.
Like comfortable.
It was familiar but sort of felt like starting over.
Hmm.
Well, good night.
See you tomorrow.
Bye.
I'll see you later.
I bet you jerks thought it couldn't be done.
It's pretty awesome if I say so myself.
I have no doubt you guys will agree.
The hardest part's done.
Now let's start filming.
Um, why are you dressed like that?
How dare you speak to racist feet whatever that was...
Shut up, that is so fast!
Hey, this is pretty good.
The dialogue is so intense.
I can't believe this actually came out of you, Yozara.
I'm seriously impressed.
You're like a genius or something.
Do you really like it?
I mean, well, duh.
Rika has decided that this is our script.
Next thing we need to do is cast it.
Actually, the cast is already set.
Obviously, I will play our ingenue, Kuya.
Kuya's best friend and transfer student, Herotica, will be played by Kotaka.
Oh, that's cool.
Sana, the bitter, jealous, yet questionably popular girl, will be played by meat, of course.
Huh?
Yukimura will be Nobuyuki, the shy little boy who is secretly in love with Herotica.
Okay.
Then there's Sirika, who's always playing stupid pranks on Kuya for being with Herotica.
Rika plays her.
Huh.
Kuya's annoying little sister, Mari, is going to be Maria.
Rude.
Why does she have to be annoying?
Well, is it perfect or is it perfect?
None of the above.
What's the matter, tits?
You don't like your role?
You gave yourself the lead and you made me the villain?
I didn't cast it until I re-read the script.
I just did what made the most sense.
Sana is the popular one, which means she should be devastatingly good-looking.
As much as I hate saying it, you do fit the description.
Her past doesn't make her the villain.
It makes her the more relatable character.
You said you wanted a juicy role, right?
Well, it would be nice to show my range.
Yeah, okay, I'm in.
Great.
All roles have been accepted.
Rika has a question.
Yes, Rika, you can wear your hair any way you want.
It's not about hair this time.
If we're casting based on looks and personality,
then Rika has to say that Kotaka as the stud transfer student is not the best choice.
Me?
But why not?
Herotika's personality doesn't seem to work.
He's honorable, he has a passion for justice, he's courageous, he's totally popular.
He's supposed to be funny and sociable and charming, right?
You have him written as tall and athletic with rugged features.
It's like we're twins.
Nothing about this guy sounds anything like Kotaka.
No one would ever believe it.
I didn't think it would be that noticeable.
Wait, what's that noticeable?
I was thinking the same thing.
You couldn't do a worse casting job.
The real Herotika would be offended.
If Big Brother wasn't puny, he might look like a cool guy.
Is there another reason?
Why would anyone choose Kotaka as a leading man type?
Yeah, there is actually.
It's not about the look.
It's because Kotaka and I have known each other since we were kids.
That's right, I almost forgot about that.
Kuya and Herotika were childhood friends,
so I chose my actual childhood friend to play opposite me in the film.
I figured it would be more realistic for us both.
Is there anything else I can help you with?
No, maybe a dressing room with candy?
Let me get this straight.
If you don't play Kuya,
then we don't have to cast your actual friend as the lead, right?
In fact, we may not even need that character at all.
What are you trying to say, Rika?
It's just that maybe we should all vote on the cast instead.
I can get behind that.
Hey, nobody's talking to you.
What's the matter?
Are you worried that we won't vote for you as Kuya or something?
Of course I'm not.
I know you guys want this movie to be good, too.
Okay, all the votes are tallied, and this is what we've got.
If I'm playing Kuya, that means I'm the lead?
This is so ridiculous.
Yay!
I get to be the bitter, bossy, booby, popular pretty girl!
Yep, that is awkward.
No, Luyuki, so Rika's playing a young boy?
What the crap?
You've got to be kidding me!
How did I go from the male lead to playing the little sister?
This is your fault, isn't it?
It's not like I had a choice.
Plus, I thought you might enjoy a challenge.
Well, you're wrong, and what do you mean you didn't have a choice?
Can we discuss why you're yelling at me?
I'm not the only one who voted.
Who else voted for me, then?
Me!
What? Why?
Because it looks like fun!
You're big brother every day.
I wanted to see you be someone different.
Doesn't get any more non-brother than being a sister!
Rika thinks there may have been ulterior motives for voting the way we did.
At least no one can accuse us of typecasting.
Yeah, I don't know that this is what we're going for.
Shouldn't we take another vote?
I mean, it's gonna be fine.
You'll make an amazing lead, Yukimura.
Thank you.
I promise to make you proud, sir.
Of course you will.
I just need to figure out how to get into my role.
I guess I'll change it to a little brother.
It's not going to hurt the story if we switch genders.
Now what?
Do you want to play a little boy?
Uh, no.
I just kind of feel bad.
Huh?
Well, you wrote the whole script, and I just made even more work for you.
Hold on.
I feel like you're showing signs of having a soul, and it's creeping me out a bit.
Rude.com!
I-I just liked your script, okay?
It's pretty awesome.
Ugh.
Thank you.
I mean, it's not a big deal to change a sister to a brother.
The script's basically the same.
Oh, you sure?
Well, then, I guess it's fine.
What the hell is happening?
This is a completely different story now.
Why?
It's still the same.
Um, no, it is not.
Who the heck is this Kotaro guy?
Kuya's little brother.
I know, but why are they suddenly twins?
Mari was never a twin.
Why now?
What are you trying to pull?
This is not what I signed up for.
A little suspicious how he went from a side character to pretty much the new lead.
This was supposed to be about Kuya and Herodika's friendship, but now you have them hating each other.
Yeah, because they were never that close to begin with.
I just forgot to write it in, okay?
But you said they were best friends.
No, Herodika just thought of Kuya as a friend of a best friend.
He knew her, but that's about as far as it went.
She was actually friends with Kotaro, who was friends with Herodika, so they all hung out together.
That sounds like a lot to keep up with.
What's wrong with letting all three of them be friends?
Because friend of a friend does not mean friend.
It just means acquaintances.
Huh?
Besides, I don't want to write about a three-way friendship.
It's too hard.
It's two friends and their friend.
I guess I kind of understand what you mean.
That doesn't make sense.
Why not keep Kuya and Herodika best friends and make Kotaro the odd one out since he's the new character?
That way you don't have to change the story.
Sorry, it won't work.
Why not?
Because it's much more natural for him to get along with Kotaro.
I mean, since that's who Kotaka's gonna be playing.
I get it now.
You just want Kotaka to play whoever your friend is in the film.
Yeah, it makes sense that way.
No, it doesn't.
You're just recreating the past instead of telling a story.
What did you say to me?
Well, what past am I recreating?
Uh, the past of you and Kotaka being close friends?
That shouldn't matter now.
You should be trying to tell a new original story,
not using this movie as a way to try to turn back time.
How dare you?
That isn't true.
Stop being so dramatic.
You're the only one being dramatic and obsessing about the past.
Quit trying so hard to hold on to it.
You're dragging everyone else down with you and it's not fair.
Yozra, are you okay?
It's your fault.
If you weren't here, I wouldn't have to feel like this.
Jerk, you just wait.
Someday you're gonna know exactly how this feels!
Yozra, come back!
I didn't mean for that to happen.
I'm sorry.
This sucks.
Maybe I shouldn't have been so honest.
I was only trying to get through to her.
Why can't she let the past go?
I'm sorry.
Yozra.
Ah!
What are you doing?
Nothing.
I forgot my bag in gym class today.
That's all.
Sucks when that happens.
What do you think?
Should Herodica be best friends with Kuya or Kotaro?
Be honest.
It makes no difference to me.
I just want the story to be good.
I know.
I just...
I want it to be you.
Huh?
I didn't quite catch that.
Tell me which is more important to you.
Our friendship the way it was ten years ago or the way it is now.
I don't know how to answer that.
They're both different.
If they're so different, then you should have a preference, right?
I guess I need inspiration.
What's your pick?
Would you go back to ten years ago or are you happy with the way things are?
Um, well, that's a no-brainer for me.
I'd go back ten years.
Does that mean the present isn't as important?
Uh-huh.
It's hard to explain.
I know what you mean.
Yeah.
My toads love it.
You really shouldn't be shocked for my ability to make adjustments.
Rika is so excited and relieved.
This story is ten thousand times better than the last one you wrote.
Good job.
Rika was worried you were going to change Kotaro.
Thank goodness you didn't.
It's perfect this way.
It's obvious you worked very hard on this.
Thank you.
Thank you for your feedback.
Okay, well, if no one else has any other questions, I say we get moving.
I'm ready to film this thing.
How about you?
We're going to rule.
I hope I do your story justice.
This movie has no choice but to be the best because I'm in it.
Shut up, Titzilla.
This story sounds familiar for some reason.
Dear Mademoiselle Yozora, you look so very sad and alone over there.
Oh, sing. I was happy that she was able to explore and learn more about her love story.
We hope we helped, but fair is fair, my sweet.
Next time, share the secrets of your heart or bedroom.
Now to sleep, my Stephanie. Je t'aime always.
Oh, dear Jonathan, a million times, je t'aime.
Please join us next time for Stray Cats Overheat.
Wait just a minute. My loins are overheating!
Oh, c'est bon! C'est bon!
Thank you.